A Finding Aid to the Duane Hanson Papers, 1935-2006, in the Archives of American Art aaa.hansduan
Archives of American Art
- Printed Material, 1958-1994; Series 7; 4 Linear feet Boxes 9-14, 15
  - Magazines, 1970s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 1-6)
  - Magazines, 1970s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Printed Materials, circa 1975-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Photographs, 1978-1990; Series 8; 0.1 Linear feet Box 14
  There are photographs of Duane Hanson and his father Dewey, and of works of art, as well as slides.
  - Dewey and Duane Hanson, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Contact Sheets, circa 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Works of Art, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Slides, circa 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)